

## Prajaktta Baravkar

### ation Associate

An Experienced banker with excellent mathematical and analytical skills as well as a devotion to Operation Department. Two and half years of experience in Operations and Service Department at Top Finance Institutes. Maintained 90% satisfaction rate from banking customers.

### **Employment History**

### Poonawalla Fincorp Ltd.

DECEMBER 2020 — PRESENT

- Working as Senior Executive in Accounts and Operations.
- Operational activities like Generating TDS, Repayment schedule, statement of account, swapping of account, sanction letter, interest certificate, TDS and excess amount refunds.
- · Bank reconciliations.
- Loan cancellations, adjustments and rectifications, loan closures, part and foreclosure payment updates.
- Generate timely management information system (MIS) on regular basis.

#### **HDFC Bank.**

OCTOBER 2019 — DECEMBER 2020

- Manage HNI clients and achieve high customer satisfaction and delight.
- Provide in-depth knowledge about HDFC Bank products and services to include loans, insurance, investment options, credit cards etc.
- Provide banking and finance support to the clients.
- To develop and maintain long term service relation with the customers.
- To do data analysis and infer the needs of customers and provide tailor made customized service to the customers.

### Education

### MBA in Banking and Finance Services, Ajeenkya D.Y. Patil University

AUGUST 2018 — JUNE 2020

Graduated with 8.00 CGPA in the Course

1. Project- Introduction To Mutual Funds (2020)

Detailed understanding of Mutual Funds and its scope. To understand various types of funds and there benefits. Study on Asset Management Company (AMC) in India.

2. Project- Case Study on What to Focus: Marketing or Operation – HDFC Bank (2020)

Detail understanding of the role of Personal Banker/Relationship Manager in banking sector. To understand perception of the customer and how company generates business through marketing. In-depth study on HDFC Bank such as Human Resource, Management, Technology, Operations and Marketing Departments

3. Project - Equity Analysis: Created a Portfolio of 15 stocks. (2019)

### **Details**

Pune, India 9146010392

@gmail.com

### **Skills**

Finnacle Software

Oracle CCA

Finnone LMS

**CRM Dynamics** 

Microsoft Office

Communication

**Problem Solving** 

**Quantitative Analysis** 

Data Analysis

### **Hobbies**

Photography, Travelling, Painting

### Languages

English

Hindi

Marathi

Created a portfolio for investor which helps to choose right scheme Identified the best stocks in stock market. Compared the stocks based on their risk and return.

## Bachelor of Business Management, Garware College of Commerce, Pune

AUGUST 2014 — DECEMBER 2017

Graduated with 63.00%.

# Project- Study of Top 10 Equity Schemes from Top 10 Asset Management Company (AMC)

P Identified the best Equity Schemes of Top Asset Management Company (AMC). To help the investor to choose right scheme and to make sound decisions

## Higher Secondary School Certificate, Akutai Kalyani Girls Jr. College, Pune

JUNE 2012 — MAY 2014

Completed 12th grade with 60%.

### Secondary School Certificate., The Army Public School, Pune

APRIL 2012

Completed 10 th grade with 76.00%.

### TRAINING AND CERTIFICATE

#### National Institute of Securities Markets.

DECEMBER 2018

Mutual Fund Distributors Certification Examination.

### **National Institute of Securities Markets.**

SEPTEMBER 2018

Securities Operations and Risk Management Certification Examination.

### **Insurance Regulatory and Development Authority**

DATE

Certification In Insurance Regulatory Development Authority

### **Extra-curricular activities**

### **Intra College Competition**

Ranked 1<sup>st</sup> in Intra College Asset Management Company (AMC) Project (2018)